





Seeking roles in/as Scrum Master , Business Analysis, Business Consulting, Software Engineering, Software Development, Web Development, Project Management, Change Management, Automation Testing, Requirement

Gathering, Programming, Python, Rally, HTML, SQL, CSS, C

Total Experience: 3 Year(s) 8 Month(s)

Notice Period: Currently Serving Notice Period Highest Degree: B.Tech/B.E. [Computers]

Pref. Location: Bengaluru / Bangalore, Gurgaon, Noida

Functional Area: IT Software - Application Programming /

Current Location: Gurgaon

Current Designation: Scrum Master

Current Company: Aricent Technologies

Role: Business Analyst

Industry: IT-Software/Software Services

Marital Status: Single/unmarried

Key Skills: Business Analyst, Business Analysis, Business Consulting, Software Engineering, Software Development, Web Development, Project Management, Change Management, Requirement Gathering, Scrum

Master, Rally, SQL, C, Scrum, CSM, PSM, Agile, Agile Project Management

Verified : Number | Email - id

Last Active: 20-Jan-21 Last Modified: 20-Jan-21

Jump to Section

Work Experience | Education | IT Skills |

Summary

Total 3.7+ years of exp. working as a Scrum Master that involves conducting various agile ceremonies such as Daily Standups, Sprint Planning, Sprint Retrospective and reviewing/ mapping the User Stories.

Experience in working as a Business Analyst that involves gathering requirements.

Good coding knowledge skills in C and Python.

Experience in creation of Test Estimations, Detailed Test Plan, High Level Business Scenarios, Test Cases, Test Data, Test Execution and Test Status Reporting.

Excellent Understanding of SQL.

Experience in automation testing.

Expertise in interaction with the clients directly, conducting weekly call and sharing the weekly status report that depicts the project's progress.

Effective communication, worked collaboratively to achieve strict timelines, motivating the team/myself to work effectively. Standardized training and reporting process in testing division leading to better management and effective communication.

Work Experience

Aricent Technologies as Scrum Master

May 2017 to Till Date

Cisco Unity Connection (December 2019 to current)

Project Description Voicemail Messaging System

- * Working as a Scrum Master where I am involved in conducting daily stand-ups, Sprint Planning and Sprint Retrospective. Also, involved to review and map the User Stories.
- * Worked in automation testing on TCL framework and took the automation pass results to 99%.
- * Innovated the Test Planning by introducing the Mndmaps which decreased the time spent in creating and reading the Test Plan.

Cisco CUPS 4G Advanced (July 2019 - December 2019)

Project Description

- * Developing the 4G advanced architecture
- * Worked in defects fixing for the 4G advanced Control Plane User Plane separation in CUPS.
- * Directly worked with the customer to resolve the defects and met the timelines.

Prototype Project for a client (March 2019 - June 2019)

Project Description: Detecting emotions of people through camera and finding the number of people in a queue to raise alarm to the admin in a multi store for better offline store customer experience. Used object detection using Machine Learning through Neural Networks.

- * Worked as a Business Analyst in this project. Requirements were gathered from the client.
- * Collaborated with the team and helped them understand the requirements. Daily progress of the project was monitored. Any changes in the functionality was analysed and decisions were taken accordingly. Took the project to end to end completion.

Cisco Unity Connection (May 2017 to March 2019)
Project Description Voicemail Messaging System



Important

 Using Free CV Search you have access to featured candidate profiles of Naukri. You can browse through the profiles and email the candidates of your choice directly using the email option provided. To prevent misuse of candidate information, contact details and attached resume of the candidates have been withheld.

- * Worked in C into security modules and Python testing scripts.
- * Worked in front end to develop Branding pages of Cisco Unity Solution.
- * Collaboratively worked with the client to give end to end Demo to the features delivered.
- * Shell scripts were also written for deployment of an application.
- * Deployed the bug tracking software, Bugzilla.

^ Back to Top

Education

UG: B.Tech/B.E. (Computers) from Guru Gobind Singh Indraprastha University (GGSIU) in 2016

Other Qualifications/Certifications/Programs:

Professional Scrum Master

^ Back to Top

IT Skills

	Skill Name	Version	Last Used	Experience
	HTML5, CSS, Rally, Agilegaadi, Xmind			
	C, Python, SQL, Windows, Linux			
	Microsoft Excel, R			

^ Back to Top

Languages Known

Language	Proficiency	Read	Write	Speak
English				
Hindi				

^ Back to Top

Affirmative Action

Work Authorization

Physically Challenged: No

Job Type: Permanent Employment Status: Full time

^ Back to Top

Careers - About Us - Clients - Terms & Conditions - FAQ's - Contact Us - Report a Problem - Site Map - Resources
Our Partners: Jeevansathi Matrimonials - ICICIcommunities.org - 99acres - Real Estate In India
All rights reserved © 2021 Info Edge India Ltd.

Careers - About Us - Clients - Terms & Conditions - FAQ's - Contact Us - Report a Problem - Site Map - Resources
Our Partners: Jeevansathi Matrimonials - ICIClcommunities.org - 99acres - Real Estate In India
All rights reserved © 2021 Info Edge India Ltd.